Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
If God be for us, who can be against us? Nobody!
Thank you.
Let's look at 2 Corinthians 12 about Apostle Paul.
and I will take the reading from verse 7.
"And lest I be exalted above measure, by the abundance of the revelations,
a thorn in the flesh was given to me, a messenger of satan to buffet me."
Verse 8.
"Concerning this thing, I pleaded with the Lord three times
that it might depart from me."
Verse 9.
"And He said to me, 'My grace is sufficient for you.
For my strength is made perfect in weakness'.
Therefore, most gladly, I would rather boast in my infirmities
that the power of Christ may rest upon me."
Let's stop here.
In this text now, Paul knew that his challenges were to correct him from being proud.
You know, when you read down, you will see 'conceited'.
He knew his challenges were to correct him.
Some of the reasons we look back is because of the mistakes or pain of the past.
Paul knew that his challenges...
When we say 'challenges', it could be of sickness, poverty, hardship,
backwardness, limitation in progress or any foolish thing.
Paul knew his challenges were to correct him from being proud or conceited.
In that text, when you read down, from the beginning to the end,
That was why he was not offended;
that was why he did not look at God in a bad light.
Like many of us - "I pay my tithe; I go to church."
Tell your neighbour, Don't give up when God corrects you.
I can't hear you.
Don't give up when God corrects you.
Be encouraged that God loves you enough to correct you.
As if somebody says, "Please come here! Why should you do this? It is wrong!"
You say, "Why should this man shout on me like this?"
No, no, no! He loves you.
The more that correction, the more your greatness.
Be encouraged when God corrects you.
Be encouraged that God loves you enough to correct you.
Tell your neighbour: Be encouraged that God loves you enough to correct you.
Paul knew that his challenges - the thorn in his flesh - were to correct him
from being proud, arrogant and conceited.
Whatever you are facing,
whatever your challenges are as a Christian -
it could be poverty, this or that.
You can be sick; your sickness is not like others' but for the glory of God.
Others' sickness is to kill them, destroy them
but our own is to reform us for a better position,
to keep us for a new level in life.
Whatever you are facing - it could be poverty or whatever - as a Christian is a way of correction.
Tell your neighbour.
Whatever situation you are facing, whatever your challenges are
as a Christian, are a way of correction.
Your challenges are not meant to destroy you.
Your challenges may be to reform you for a better position.
Your challenges may be to keep you for a new level in life.
Your challenges may be to strengthen your desire for God.
What are your challenges?
Tell your neighbour: See your challenges as a reason for believing God
just as you see your good times.
See your challenges as a reason for believing God
In your good times, you dance and say, "Thank You, Jesus!".
So when that hard time comes too, "Thank You, Jesus!".
Paul saw his challenges, the thorn in his flesh,
as a reason for believing God just as he did in his good times.
That is why he went to God three times.
Each time the Lord said, "My grace is suffient for you", and he did not give up.
Another time the Lord said, "My grace is sufficient for you".
Another time...
Each time is equal to hundred times.
For summary, one time is equal to hundred times,
two times - 200 times, three times - 300 times.
Job saw his challenges as a reason for believing God
just as he did in his good times.
Be encouraged when you are corrected by God.
Tell your neighbour.
I can't hear you.
Be encouraged when you are corrected by God.
Don't give up when God corrects you.
Be encouraged that God loves you enough to correct you.
Thank you.
Hallelujah.
Honour God just as you honour Him in your good times -
honour Him in your situation.
Jesus must be honoured
Jesus must be honoured in my life
Every day
Jesus must be honoured
Jesus must be honoured in my life
Every day
If Jesus must be honoured every day,
remember our spiritual walk with the Lord -
good and hard times.
Jesus must be honoured
Jesus must be honoured in my life
Every day
Jesus must be honoured
Jesus must be honoured in my life
Every day
Remain silent and think about your life.
This is the hindrance you are having.
Your belief, once you accept Jesus as your Lord and Saviour -
bed of roses.
So right now, think about your life.
Christianity is all about 'relationship'.
We are not religious people; we are Christians.
If you must be a Christian, you must be ready for this relationship.
Our relationship with Christ is in both good and hard times.
Christianity is all about 'relationship'.
It is different from religion.
Religious people, when they are facing hard times,
they lament, they murmur.
They begin to see God in a bad light.
That is religious people.
But we Christians, we see our challenges as a reason for believing in God,
just as we see our good times.
Christians seek not yet repose
Hear thy guardian angel say
Thou art in the midst of foes
Watch and pray
Christians seek not yet repose
Hear thy guardian angel say
Thou art in the midst of foes
Watch and pray
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.